sgrecruiters.com 2010-05-07

# Recruitment Agency - Privacy Policy

SG Recruiters Group Pte Ltd takes your privacy seriously. This privacy statement discloses the type of information we gather, how we use it and how to correct or change it.  
 **  
How we collect information?**

Your personal information is collected when you provide it to us, such as when you register in our websites, provide feedback, make enquiry or sign up for an email newsletter. We may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you had provided to us. We collect and store your information so that we might improve our communication with you.  
 **  
What do we do with collected information?**

SG Recruiters Group Pte Ltd do not sell or disclose your personal data provided to us, to any advertisers or other third parties for marketing, promotional and other purposes. We may do joint promotion with these entities but we do not disclose any information that could be used to identify you personally.

When you provide us with your personal data, you may expect SG Recruiters Group Pte Ltd to contact you by mail or email, for the purpose of:

\- Providing you the updates in the career/recruitment industry (such as monthly newsletter or articles)  
\- Providing you the updates in our company's coming events  
\- Providing you more information about HR related products or services (may come in the form of advertisement, sponsored by the advertisers)  
\- We will only make your personally identifiable information available to any 3rd party when we have your consent to share the information.

If you have any concerns, [contact us](http://sgrecruiters.com/main/index.php?option=com_contact&view=contact&id=1&Itemid=53 "contact us"). 

### Register Now

Register with us today! Deposit your resume with us and our recruitment consultants will get in touch with you. 

### About our team

Our recruitment team is committed to offer our clients with the most suitable human resources solution and enhancing career opportunities for our candidates. We believe in creating unlimited opportunities for all, success to our clients and excellent career growth to our candidates. 

### Our Credentials

At SG Recruiters Group, we've built our reputation from scratch. Since the proof is in the pudding, we let our clients do the talking for us. 

## Singapore Recruitment Agencies. Accounting Jobs. Employment Services. Singapore Human Resource. Career Opportunities. Job Agencies. Part Time Jobs. Recruitment Agency. Singapore Jobs. Employment Agency. Recruitment Services.

Copyright © 2008. SG Recruiters Group. All Rights Reserved. /
